[
  {
    "question": "Evaluate the expression <br> of 2x + 9 when x = 7",
    "correctAnswer": "23",
    "options": [
      "21",
      "24",
      "23",
      "18"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Evaluate the expression <br> of 2x + 4 when x = 4",
    "correctAnswer": "12",
    "options": [
      "12",
      "14",
      "9",
      "16"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Evaluate the expression <br> of 5x + 3 when x = 2",
    "correctAnswer": "13",
    "options": [
      "9",
      "13",
      "12",
      "11"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Evaluate the expression <br> of 4x + 1 when x = 7",
    "correctAnswer": "29",
    "options": [
      "31",
      "32",
      "25",
      "29"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Evaluate the expression <br> of 1x + 3 when x = 1",
    "correctAnswer": "4",
    "options": [
      "4",
      "7",
      "8",
      "0"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Evaluate the expression <br> of 4x + 4 when x = 8",
    "correctAnswer": "36",
    "options": [
      "36",
      "37",
      "34",
      "33"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Evaluate the expression <br> of 3x + 3 when x = 5",
    "correctAnswer": "18",
    "options": [
      "20",
      "14",
      "15",
      "18"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Evaluate the expression <br> of 5x + 5 when x = 3",
    "correctAnswer": "20",
    "options": [
      "23",
      "20",
      "21",
      "16"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Evaluate the expression <br> of 2x + 2 when x = 10",
    "correctAnswer": "22",
    "options": [
      "25",
      "21",
      "27",
      "22"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Evaluate the expression <br> of 4x + 7 when x = 9",
    "correctAnswer": "43",
    "options": [
      "39",
      "42",
      "41",
      "43"
    ]
  }
]